redrightvideos.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy - Red Right Videos

Like all commercial websites, Red Right Videos needs to know who its audience is for advertising and administrative purposes. At the same time, we understand that our users value their privacy. This policy is designed to balance your right to be left alone with our desire for certain basic data about your computer system.

### Log Files

If you don’t register, the information we collect will be limited to your general Internet settings or “log file.” Log files typically include your operating system, your ISP and IP address, the type of browser you’re using, the resolution of your monitor, and the pages on our site that you clicked through while visiting.

### Comments and E-mails

Red Right Videos will not record your e-mail address unless (a) you register to post comments on our site, or (b) you send us e-mail.

If you register to post comments, you must provide us with a valid e-mail address. We won’t share it with anyone (except our contractors and under certain extraordinary circumstances described below), but we will cancel your registration and block you from re-registering with that address if you violate our terms of use.

If you send us e-mail, your e-mail address will usually be displayed at the top of your message. Red Right Videos retains most of the messages it receives, so your address likely will remain on record in our e-mail archives. These archives are stored on servers owned and operated by third parties such as Google Inc.

### Cookies

Red Right Videos may use cookies to record your log file and, if you’ve registered to comment, to remember your Red Right Videos login and password for you. We may also grant permission to our advertisers to use cookies in their ads. Cookies are small text files placed automatically on your hard drive by your web browser when you visit certain websites in order to make those sites easier to use. You can configure your browser to disable cookies and/or to alert you when new ones are being sent, but please note that some features of our site might not work properly if you do so.

 **Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website or open our emails. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at[www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) and Networking Advertising Initiative at [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

### Disclosure

Red Right Videos generally will not disclose information we have collected from your log file except to our contractors and in the aggregate, as part of demographic analyses to help advertisers or other third parties better understand our audience (e.g., “30% of our users use Mozilla Firefox”). In addition, we may disclose information about your individual log file or, if you’ve registered to comment, your e-mail address in the following two extraordinary circumstances: (a) if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so by law, or to comply with a court order or judicial proceeding; or (b) if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to defend the legal rights and interests of Red Right Videos, or its individual contributors; or (c) if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to protect the site’s infrastructure (for example, to investigate denial of service attacks.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, if you send us an e-mail message, Red Right Videos will assume that you consent to your message – including your e-mail address – being reprinted in full on our website should we deem it worthy of publication. If you do not consent to your e-mail being made public, please say so in your message.

### Threatening communications

Notwithstanding any of the foregoing provisions, Red Right Videos reserves the right to collect, disclose, and publicize user data, IP addresses, e-mail addresses, and any and all other personal information about anyone who, in any format or by any medium, including comments left on RedRightVideos.com, threatens himself or others. Red Right Videos will not honor requests for privacy attached to such threatening communications. Red Right Videos further reserves the right to share any such data and information related to threatening communications with any local, state, and federal law enforcement agency, either voluntarily or in response to an agency’s simple request.

### Miscellaneous

This privacy policy applies to RedRightVideos.com. It does not apply to our advertisers (including advertisers who use cookies in their ads on our site), online merchandisers, websites to which we link, or any other third party, none of which are owned or operated by Red Right Videos, and about which we make no warranties or representations. For information about a third party’s privacy policy, please consult their individual website.

Red Right Videos reserves the right to transfer or assign the data collected from our users in the event of a merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the event of bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, Red Right Videos may not be able to control how our user data is disposed of.

This privacy policy may be revised from time to time. Please check this page periodically for updates. Your use of our site on any given date indicates your acceptance to the terms of this policy as of that date.
